<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.0">Jekyll</generator>
  
  
  <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" />
  <updated>2017-10-01T06:17:11+00:00</updated>
  <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay//</id>

  
    <title type="html">satirical hearsay</title>
  

  
    <subtitle>Local news of global origins. Published sporadically.</subtitle>
  

  
    <author>
        <name>John Smith</name>
      
      
    </author>
  

  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">G.B. Road To Be Renamed G.S.T. Road</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/10/01/gb-road-renamed-gst-road/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="G.B. Road To Be Renamed G.S.T. Road" />
      <published>2017-10-01T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-10-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/10/01/gb-road-renamed-gst-road</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/10/01/gb-road-renamed-gst-road/">&lt;p&gt;“Aisi chudai kabhi na kiya aur na hi dekha”, said popular &lt;em&gt;vendor&lt;/em&gt; Miss Bubbly (name changed to protect identity).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Goods and Services Tax (GST) reform hangs as a &lt;del&gt;swollen penis inside the pants&lt;/del&gt; double-edged sword over the heads of the &lt;em&gt;entrepreneurs&lt;/em&gt; of Delhi’s infamous red light district – G.B. Road. With the services being offered in the area finally coming under the special services bracket of the tax, the life and work of the &lt;em&gt;artists&lt;/em&gt; in the area has finally been legalized. However, the services are taxed at a giggling 69% which has left the &lt;em&gt;employees&lt;/em&gt; complaining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have to say, it hurts but thoda toh mazaa aa gaya”, said a &lt;em&gt;proprietor&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Main toh abhi condom bhi nahi khareed pata hai so main safed panni aur rubberband chadha ke hi kaam chala raha hai”, said another.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="english" />
      
        <category term="India" />
      
        <category term="political" />
      
        <category term="lifestyle" />
      
        <category term="shorts" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">“Aisi chudai kabhi na kiya aur na hi dekha”, said popular vendor Miss Bubbly (name changed to protect identity). The Goods and Services Tax (GST) reform hangs as a swollen penis inside the pants double-edged sword over the heads of the entrepreneurs of Delhi’s infamous red light district – G.B. Road. With the services being offered in the area finally coming under the special services bracket of the tax, the life and work of the artists in the area has finally been legalized. However, the services are taxed at a giggling 69% which has left the employees complaining. “I have to say, it hurts but thoda toh mazaa aa gaya”, said a proprietor. “Main toh abhi condom bhi nahi khareed pata hai so main safed panni aur rubberband chadha ke hi kaam chala raha hai”, said another.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">Portal To POK Found Under Railway FOB</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/29/portal-to-POK-found-under-railway-FOB/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Portal To POK Found Under Railway FOB" />
      <published>2017-09-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-09-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/29/portal-to-POK-found-under-railway-FOB</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/29/portal-to-POK-found-under-railway-FOB/">&lt;h4&gt;Shiv Sena followers kill 100 militants out of exasperation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the frustratingly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ndtv.com/mumbai-news/elphinstone-station-stampede-moments-that-led-to-stampede-caught-in-mobile-phone-video-1756740&quot;&gt;deadly stampede at Mumbai’s Elphinstone railway station&lt;/a&gt; yesterday, the Rail Ministry held a high-level meeting to avert future crises. The committee decided to reconstruct all foot overbridges in the City of (Ghastly) Dreams on high priority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To showcase their pragmatism, the Railways began to tear down all the bridges at once; this while tenders are still being invited for the construction of the replacement bridges. “Kaal kare so aaj kar, aaj kare so ab”, said a senior official.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the steadfast working deserves attention, reality has turned into fiction at Andheri West railway station as workers seem to have found a portal to Pakistan Occupied Kashmir (POK) from underneath the overbridge site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An onlooker and a certified Potterhead remarked, “This is like Platform Number 9 2/11.” We quickly moved away from her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pappu Nandan, who had just come to the city from his village to start a new life joined the construction workers soon as he deboarded the train. “I was sitting on top of the guard bogie and saw some people tearing down something as the train pulled into the station. I was immediately attracted towards it because mujhe laga ki mandir banana hoga wahan”, he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was only when he was about to take a chai break that his foot got stuck in the rubble and the floor around him began to sink in like quick sand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I was knocked out but when I got up I saw that I was stuck in a trench. As I climbed out I was surrounded by a bunch of goatherders. I asked them where I was and they said in Pakistan. Well they said Azad Kashmir but I know there is no such thing so it must have been Pakistan only. I knew what I had to do, so I took a stone and killed all of them North Indian bastards. If they want to live in Azad Kashmir they should go to Pakistan. Bloody terrorists.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vidhu Vinod Chopra has already claimed the rights for a film on Pappu’s lifestory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Shiv Sena was extremely frustrated by this incident. “These bastards were sitting under our nose all this time!”, said an angry &lt;del&gt;militant&lt;/del&gt; supporter. A “Sena” of 72 men rushed into the portal and killed 100 militants on the other side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Prime Minster was extremely pleased by this discovery and took to Twitter to express his elation –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
Bhai wah. Ek dum kadak. &lt;a&gt;#QuantumIndia #SmartCity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Modi Ji (@UNApprovedBestPM) &lt;a&gt;Feb 28, 2002&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The portal site is being touted unofficially as the Indian equivalent of Area 51 – Khand 420. The Indian Army has taken charge of the site and has put orange traffic cones around it to prevent any illegal occupation.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="english" />
      
        <category term="India" />
      
        <category term="political" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Shiv Sena followers kill 100 militants out of exasperation After the frustratingly deadly stampede at Mumbai’s Elphinstone railway station yesterday, the Rail Ministry held a high-level meeting to avert future crises. The committee decided to reconstruct all foot overbridges in the City of (Ghastly) Dreams on high priority. To showcase their pragmatism, the Railways began to tear down all the bridges at once; this while tenders are still being invited for the construction of the replacement bridges. “Kaal kare so aaj kar, aaj kare so ab”, said a senior official.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">Saudi King Regrets Letting Women Drive</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/28/saudi-king-regrets-letting-women-drive/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Saudi King Regrets Letting Women Drive" />
      <published>2017-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/28/saudi-king-regrets-letting-women-drive</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/28/saudi-king-regrets-letting-women-drive/">&lt;h4&gt;Male drivers lose jobs to better women drivers&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Women in the country gained the right to drive early last month in a move celebrated by feminist activist groups all over the world. However, an unsettling account has come up in the wake of protests by male drivers who are losing their jobs to women as the fairer sex has proved to be a more reliable and safer operator behind the wheel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who would have thought this would happen? If you ask Salim Smith, personal advisor to the King of Saudi Arabia, he would say – “I told you so.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The situation is such that many of the leading taxicab and transporation companies have begun to prefer women drivers over all men regardless of experience. “Women are just too good at this thing!”, exclaimed one mysteriously jubilant taxicab owner in Riyadh. Another told us that he only hires women truck drivers for his shipping company since they are reliable and have years of experience of surviving under harsh conditions. “It’s almost as if we did them a favour by not letting them drive all these years”, he added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Witnessing the widespread protests in the country by the disgruntled darker sex, Salim Smith took to Twitter to provide an insider’s account of why women weren’t previously allowed to drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
It was a well thought-out strategy to stop women. They were always too good. Advised the King to not risk it. Didn't listen.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Salim Smith (@RealSamSmith) &lt;a&gt;Jul 22, 2018&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turns out that the King had conducted experiments behind closed doors back in 1968 and 1992 wherein female drivers were pitted against their male counterparts in a classic MTV Battle of the Sexes fashion. The women thrashed the men ridiculously in all competitions – something that was deeply unsettling for the fragile male ego of the Saudis. It was suggested (by Salim and his father before him) that women be barred from driving until they forget how to drive. The hope was that the “good driving gene” would soon phase out of the Saudi women’s physiology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Charles Darwin failed us”, said Salim. “I told the king to wait for another generation. He wanted to impress Ivanka. And now look what it has wrought”, he added wiping his tears with his sleeve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When approached for a comment, the King’s staff told us that the King would issue a public statement on his Twitter account which we have provided below –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
It was all a f**KING mistake.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; KING SMITH (@KINGDONG) &lt;a&gt;Jul 20, 2018&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-women-driving-accidents/saudi-women-to-be-allowed-to-drive-from-age-18-same-as-men-idUSKCN1C31PE&quot;&gt;Saudi minister says adding women drivers will reduce car crashes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="english" />
      
        <category term="world" />
      
        <category term="lifestyle" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Male drivers lose jobs to better women drivers Women in the country gained the right to drive early last month in a move celebrated by feminist activist groups all over the world. However, an unsettling account has come up in the wake of protests by male drivers who are losing their jobs to women as the fairer sex has proved to be a more reliable and safer operator behind the wheel. Who would have thought this would happen? If you ask Salim Smith, personal advisor to the King of Saudi Arabia, he would say – “I told you so.”</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">PM left saffron-faced after a series of Twitter embarrassments</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/28/pm-left-saffron-faced/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PM left saffron-faced after a series of Twitter embarrassments" />
      <published>2017-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-09-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/28/pm-left-saffron-faced</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/28/pm-left-saffron-faced/">&lt;h4&gt;New India 2002?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Prime Minster today had to face great embarrasment after launching the ruling party’s New India campaign. In what was supposed to be a visionary target set for the year 2022 (when the country celebrates 75 years of covert subjugation of western powers), he tweeted the year 2002 instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “accidental” typo led to a massive (yet unsurprising) shift in the rhetoric attached with the campaign as supporters of nationalist sentiments thought their dreams had finally come true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the original tweet has since been removed, we provide a screenshot below –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
The year is 2002 and India is the greatest country in the world. &lt;a&gt;#NewIndia2002&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Modi Ji (@UNApprovedBestPM) &lt;a&gt;Feb 28, 2002&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bjpitcell.org/&quot; title=&quot;Not related to Stephen King. But equally scary.&quot;&gt;IT Clown Circus&lt;/a&gt; of BJP went into turbo-charged mode soon as the tweet was issued and quickly published a list of addresses of Muslim households on its website along with an instructions manual on effective rioting written in Sanskrit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The top-brass of BJP and RSS were visibly jubilant and captured the ecstatic emotions in 140-character ultimatums –&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
1992, 2002, 2022. Ghanti wahin bajayenge. &lt;a&gt;#NewIndia2002&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Advani Group (@ArchaicLivesMatter) &lt;a&gt;Dec 6, 1992&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
Ey ganpat, chal daaru laa. &lt;a&gt;#NewIndia2002&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Amit Paan Masala (@12ShahShahShah) &lt;a&gt;Jul 25, 2010&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
Summer mein khaki shorts, winter mein laga ke shots. &lt;a&gt;#NewIndia2002&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Mohan (@BhagwatSabDekhRahaHai) &lt;a&gt;Dec 6, 1992&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; Panna Lal Kasai, a shakha worker from Varanasi said, &quot;हम तोह त्रिशूल निकाल के मस्जिद की तरफ चल दिए थे पर फिर कोई पीछे से बोले कि नहीं ऐसा गलती से हो गया है तोह हम रुक गए ... पर अब त्रिशूल तोह निकाल ही लिए थे तोह हम मौलवी साहब की बकरी मार ले आये&quot; (I took my trident out and was already on my way towards the mosque when someone said that it was a false alarm. So I stole the maulvi's goat instead.) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the frenzy lasted only a couple of hours, the country as a whole is visibly unshook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related: We overheard the following conversation at the chai stall outside our office –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&quot;Bro ever since demonisation I have an emergency suitcase ready with me at all times.&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
&quot;I have already filed papers for citizenship of Fiji Islands, moving there next week.&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
&quot;Sahi hai bro. Wahan ki bandiya bahut thhaa hoti hain.&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
&quot;Yep.&quot;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="english" />
      
        <category term="India" />
      
        <category term="political" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">New India 2002? The Prime Minster today had to face great embarrasment after launching the ruling party’s New India campaign. In what was supposed to be a visionary target set for the year 2022 (when the country celebrates 75 years of covert subjugation of western powers), he tweeted the year 2002 instead. The “accidental” typo led to a massive (yet unsurprising) shift in the rhetoric attached with the campaign as supporters of nationalist sentiments thought their dreams had finally come true.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">Filmmakers Fight For Dera Chief’s Release</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/27/filmmakers-fight-for-dera-chief-release/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Filmmakers Fight For Dera Chief's Release" />
      <published>2017-09-27T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-09-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/27/filmmakers-fight-for-dera-chief-release</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/27/filmmakers-fight-for-dera-chief-release/">&lt;h4&gt;Gurmit Ram Rahim is a cultural icon claims FTII&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if the Dera Sacha Sauda saga wasn’t convoluted enough, the Film and Television Institute of India (FTII) today called a press conference to issue a memorandum to the Lucknow High Court calling for the release of dera chief Sant Guru Sri Sri Gurmit Ram Rahim Joseph Singh Insan Mahavir.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When asked for a comment, Justice Panwadi Lal of the honourable Lucknow High Court said - “Bro that’s not how this works.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John Smith, an award-winning filmmaker who currently serves as the Chief Litigation Officer for the institute said that Gurmit Ram Rahim’s approach for gaining social and cultural validation is a motivational story and deserves a wider audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It is a very post-modern concept… it breaks the existing structures of what defines a religious &lt;del&gt;cult&lt;/del&gt; sect and where the line between the bizarre and admirable lies”, said film critic Schwarz Pole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He is a cultural icon”, added Smith. “We must preserve his &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q48tagwurUw&quot;&gt;monumental contribution to Indian cinema and music industry&lt;/a&gt; the same way we preserve our 17th century Hindu ideals – he should be made Prime Minister.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He has an international standing; it’s no joke that VEVO and Zee Music Company produced his hit numbers”, he went on to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In related news, Jawaharlal Nehru Univeristy (JNU), New Delhi, had organized a 3-day lecture series titled “Dera Pheri: An investigative analysis of India’s cult worshippers” last week wherein academicians from cultural and media studies offered their viewpoints on the country’s fascination with colourful circus leaders and why this fascination seems to be dominated by the saffron colour of late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add to this great academic effort, FTII is planning to launch a 1-year long certificate course dubbed “Phir Dera Pheri” that will provide students with the necessary knowhow enabling them to reliably predict the market value of deras across the country. The course will be available in distance learning mode for a nominal subscription of ₹1100 per month. Hotstar subscribers can survey the course for free but will have to pay extra for the certificate. Jio Mobile users will receive the certification for free regardless of their wish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Prime Minister has been keeping a tab on the happenings so far and believes that the certificate course will likely create employment opportunities in the private sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
&lt;a&gt;@FTII #PhirDeraPheri&lt;/a&gt; commendable idea. Will boost private sector growth by 8% and bring fuel prices down by 1.2% &lt;a&gt;#NewIndia&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Modi Ji (@UNApprovedBestPM) &lt;a&gt;Feb 28, 2002&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FTII is the country’s premier filmmaking institute and has produced the careers of notable film actors like John Smith and Bob Smith.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="english" />
      
        <category term="India" />
      
        <category term="lifestyle" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Gurmit Ram Rahim is a cultural icon claims FTII As if the Dera Sacha Sauda saga wasn’t convoluted enough, the Film and Television Institute of India (FTII) today called a press conference to issue a memorandum to the Lucknow High Court calling for the release of dera chief Sant Guru Sri Sri Gurmit Ram Rahim Joseph Singh Insan Mahavir. When asked for a comment, Justice Panwadi Lal of the honourable Lucknow High Court said - “Bro that’s not how this works.”</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">Blue Whale Claims Another Victim</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/26/blue-whale-claims-another-victim/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Blue Whale Claims Another Victim" />
      <published>2017-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-09-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/26/blue-whale-claims-another-victim</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/26/blue-whale-claims-another-victim/">&lt;h4&gt;The Majestic Mammal Displays Its Might Again&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Blue Whale game has claimed yet another victim here today. The victim, a 14 year old &lt;del&gt;jackass&lt;/del&gt; boy, claimed his own life by hanging himself from the balcony of his penthouse apartment in the elite S.O.B. Villas residential society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just don’t get it… He was doing okay when I saw him last year”, said the victim’s mother via Skype. “We have been sending him a Snap everyday from the beach resort where we are celebrating our 7th divorce anniversary”, she added. He would often screenshot their Snaps and add himself in the oceanic background being eaten by a blue whale. When asked if that was probably a hint of his mental state, the father who is a Food Vlogger replied, “We thought he was being ironically macabre because everyone knows blue whales don’t eat humans.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know what got to him”, said the boy’s nanny who of course is now unemployed and in search for a new &lt;del&gt;victim&lt;/del&gt; job (contact at +919866698666, salary 1.6LPM non-negotiable).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The victim’s school friends remember him as being a nihilist and unironically morbid. “We saw True Detective together and he just really vibed with Rust Cohle you know”, said one of his classmates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Students from his school have created an app in his honour that allows users to pay their respects remotely. The VR game called &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.fusion.bluewhale&amp;amp;hl=en&quot;&gt;Blue whale VR&lt;/a&gt; lets users “Discover a blue whale facts through an immersive underwater exploration (sic).” The app has received mixed reviews with a disgruntled ‘E-MMA GRILLE’ giving it a 1-star review saying - &lt;em&gt;“useless app.nothing in it. its just a blue background. You also need a reality device to view it. There is nothing to do with the suicidal issue of a girl in russia. I think there is another issue for that.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People from all over the world are paying their respects on Twitter by using the hashtag #AlwaysBlue –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
Silicon Valley is the best show on HBO right now! &lt;a&gt;#AlwaysBlue&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Jin Yang (@iamyang) &lt;a&gt;May 22, 2016&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
&lt;a&gt;#TeamIndia&lt;/a&gt; win the 3rd ODI to take an unassailable lead of 3-0 in the five-match ODI series &lt;a&gt;#INDvsAus #AlwaysBlue&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; BCCI (@BCCI) &lt;a&gt;Sep 24, 2017&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
Where can I find that &lt;a&gt;#AlwaysBlue&lt;/a&gt; game from Silicon Valley? @HBO &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Aviato San (@aviato) &lt;a&gt;Oct 9, 2014&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This incident has taken the game to the number two spot on the Victim Leaderboard, still behind the reigning champion Flappy Bird. The game still ranks the highest, for the fifth week in a row, on the New &amp;amp; Rising Charts however.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.latintimes.com/flappy-bird-murder-hoax-site-huzlers-plants-story-about-chicago-teen-killing-brother-over-high-score&quot;&gt;Teen Stabs Brother For Breaking Flappy Bird Highscore&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="english" />
      
        <category term="world" />
      
        <category term="technology" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">The Majestic Mammal Displays Its Might Again The Blue Whale game has claimed yet another victim here today. The victim, a 14 year old jackass boy, claimed his own life by hanging himself from the balcony of his penthouse apartment in the elite S.O.B. Villas residential society. “I just don’t get it… He was doing okay when I saw him last year”, said the victim’s mother via Skype. “We have been sending him a Snap everyday from the beach resort where we are celebrating our 7th divorce anniversary”, she added. He would often screenshot their Snaps and add himself in the oceanic background being eaten by a blue whale. When asked if that was probably a hint of his mental state, the father who is a Food Vlogger replied, “We thought he was being ironically macabre because everyone knows blue whales don’t eat humans.”</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">Send Your PM To Work Today</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/25/send-your-PM-to-work-today/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Send Your PM To Work Today" />
      <published>2017-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/25/send-your-PM-to-work-today</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/25/send-your-PM-to-work-today/">&lt;h4&gt;Call Your PM NOW! But don’t say anything. Your silence is what keeps him going.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Never one to let a successful PR strategy slide and always a proponent of new and immersive technology (who can forget the great hologram speech of 2014?), reports say that the Prime Minister has been fascinated by the Missed Call campaigns of late. These campaigns were seen most recently in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://isha.sadhguru.org/rally-for-rivers/participate-give-a-missed-call-your-vote-to-save-our-rivers/&quot; title=&quot;Did I misinterpret their campaign?&quot;&gt;Trees For Free&lt;/a&gt; project run by the BABA foundation but have been around since &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.huffingtonpost.in/2017/06/23/get-1-lac-votes-and-ill-clear-the-word-intercourse-in-jab-har_a_22584233/&quot; title=&quot;He said the word. Potty mouth.&quot;&gt;this sexual remark&lt;/a&gt; by the Chief Censor and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thehindu.com/news/national/tamil-nadu/%E2%80%98Missed-call%E2%80%99-campaign-makes-a-mark/article17290237.ece&quot;&gt;this seditious propaganda&lt;/a&gt; in the southern state of Tamil Nadu earlier this year. The Prime Minister’s Office today thus issued a statement stating the PM’s demand that he would do Prime Minsterley work such as brunching with international &lt;del&gt;supermodels&lt;/del&gt; dignitaries, rehearsing for his radio show and delivering &lt;em&gt;kadak&lt;/em&gt; burns in political rally speeches if and only if he receives 10 million missed calls each morning of the week; barring Sunday because that’s his rest day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In what is touted as a never seen before collaboration, Members of Parliament have cut across party lines to join the campaign as the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bjpitcell.org/&quot; title=&quot;Not related to Stephen King. But equally scary.&quot;&gt;IT Clown Circus&lt;/a&gt; of the ruling political party accidentally misspelled the online hashtag and wrote #SendYourMPToWorkToday instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phone companies are particularly pleased with this as they are now offering targeted Value Added Services (VAS) that automatically call the PM each morning for a reasonable rate of ₹5/day. To those protesting against the cost the PM tweeted -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
A cup of cutting chai + mathhi costs ₹5. Am I not worth it? &lt;a&gt;#chaipecharcha&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Modi Ji (@UNApprovedBestPM) &lt;a&gt;Feb 28, 2002&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one is as pleased as Jio Mobiles though since their offer of 100 free missed calls to all Jio Premium Elite numbers (there’s only one, you know who has it) has been a hit with the population with their subscriber count rising 666% within the last 12 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The announcement has snowballed into a massive advertising campaign with filmmakers fighting for Hello Tune rights to the PM’s mobile number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social workers, particularly of the JNU variety, have condemned the move, calling it “hilariously undemocratic” and are seeking a complete reversal. To which the PM tweeted -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt; 
Complete reversal? I'm not Kejriwal. &lt;a&gt;@AurAamZaada&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a&gt;#casualbanter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ndash; Modi Ji (@UNApprovedBestPM) &lt;a&gt;Feb 28, 2002&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon further pressure however the PMO has acknowledged the plea and has asked the reverse-campaigners to gather 11 million missed calls if they want to be taken seriously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court has chosen to remain silent on the topic perhaps because no one rung their bell.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="english" />
      
        <category term="India" />
      
        <category term="political" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Call Your PM NOW! But don’t say anything. Your silence is what keeps him going. Never one to let a successful PR strategy slide and always a proponent of new and immersive technology (who can forget the great hologram speech of 2014?), reports say that the Prime Minister has been fascinated by the Missed Call campaigns of late. These campaigns were seen most recently in the Trees For Free project run by the BABA foundation but have been around since this sexual remark by the Chief Censor and this seditious propaganda in the southern state of Tamil Nadu earlier this year. The Prime Minister’s Office today thus issued a statement stating the PM’s demand that he would do Prime Minsterley work such as brunching with international supermodels dignitaries, rehearsing for his radio show and delivering kadak burns in political rally speeches if and only if he receives 10 million missed calls each morning of the week; barring Sunday because that’s his rest day.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">PETA Issues ‘Cute or Not’ List of Dog Breeds</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/25/peta-cute-or-not/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PETA Issues 'Cute or Not' List of Dog Breeds" />
      <published>2017-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/25/peta-cute-or-not</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/25/peta-cute-or-not/">&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever been in a situation where you’re unable to decide whether a puppy is cute or not, PETA is here to help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The umbrella organization of saviours of &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; animal lives (except a few like humans and those icky slimy ones) has issued a definitive list of dog breeds that you are allowed to display unchecked emotions for. The list, dubbed ‘Cute or Not’, has been welcomed by a number of Social Media Influencers on Instagram, Twitter and Tumblr. One particular social media celebrity, John Smith of @gay&amp;amp;atheist fame, said - “This is a God-send.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teenagers across the globe heaved a sigh of relief upon hearing the announcement. One home-schooler named Adam Smith said - “PETA always do me a great concern but now PETA G O O D B O Y E n fren.”&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="english" />
      
        <category term="lifestyle" />
      
        <category term="shorts" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">If you’ve ever been in a situation where you’re unable to decide whether a puppy is cute or not, PETA is here to help. The umbrella organization of saviours of all animal lives (except a few like humans and those icky slimy ones) has issued a definitive list of dog breeds that you are allowed to display unchecked emotions for. The list, dubbed ‘Cute or Not’, has been welcomed by a number of Social Media Influencers on Instagram, Twitter and Tumblr. One particular social media celebrity, John Smith of @gay&amp;amp;atheist fame, said - “This is a God-send.” Teenagers across the globe heaved a sigh of relief upon hearing the announcement. One home-schooler named Adam Smith said - “PETA always do me a great concern but now PETA G O O D B O Y E n fren.”</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">Return of the John Smiths</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/24/return-of-the-john-smiths/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Return of the John Smiths" />
      <published>2017-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/24/return-of-the-john-smiths</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/24/return-of-the-john-smiths/">&lt;p&gt;With the advent of obstrusive Internet search engines it has become increasingly easy to stalk your high school gym teacher’s dog. With this in view, residents of Christ City, Maryland have a novel scheme to offer – change your name to John Smith.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or some other generic name like Bob or Mary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Celebrity names are also a hit with over a 100 Beyoncés and 48 Justin Biebers registered at the City Office in just the last quarter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I can be sure that anytime someone tries to stalk a Beyoncé who gave them head at a bar in L.A., they are never going to head into my direction”, said Beyoncé.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starbucks baristas have been the worst hit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Story to be continued…&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="english" />
      
        <category term="technology" />
      
        <category term="privacy" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">With the advent of obstrusive Internet search engines it has become increasingly easy to stalk your high school gym teacher’s dog. With this in view, residents of Christ City, Maryland have a novel scheme to offer – change your name to John Smith. Or some other generic name like Bob or Mary. Celebrity names are also a hit with over a 100 Beyoncés and 48 Justin Biebers registered at the City Office in just the last quarter. “I can be sure that anytime someone tries to stalk a Beyoncé who gave them head at a bar in L.A., they are never going to head into my direction”, said Beyoncé. Starbucks baristas have been the worst hit. Story to be continued…</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">यह आकाशवाणी का दिल्ली केंदर है</title>
      
      <link href="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/22/akashvani-101/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="यह आकाशवाणी का दिल्ली केंदर है" />
      <published>2017-09-22T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-09-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/22/akashvani-101</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://gsidhu.github.io/satirical-hearsay/2017/09/22/akashvani-101/">&lt;p&gt; हमारी बातों में गूंजेगी सरकार की गांड की बू | हम आप तक पहुंचाएंगे सब खबरें सब से पहले और साथ ही साथ पेश करेंगे कुछ रंगा-रंग प्रोग्राम जिससे आप का सरकार की कु-नीतियों में विश्वास बढ़ेगा | क्यों कि अकल का नाश, सब का विकास | &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; लीजिए अब पेश है ख़ास प्रोग्राम -- मन की भड़ास | &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ye Akashvani ka Dilli kendar hai&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humari baaton mein goonjegi sarkar ki gaand ki boo. Hum aap tak pahunchayeinge sab khabarein sab se pehle, aur saath hi saath pesh karenge kuchh ranga-rang program jisse aap ka sarkar ki ku-nitiyon mein vishwas badhega. Kyun ki akal ka naash, sab ka vikas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Li jiye ab pesh hai khaas program – Mann ki Bhadaas.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>John Smith</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      
        <category term="hindi" />
      
        <category term="India" />
      
        <category term="shorts" />
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">हमारी बातों में गूंजेगी सरकार की गांड की बू | हम आप तक पहुंचाएंगे सब खबरें सब से पहले और साथ ही साथ पेश करेंगे कुछ रंगा-रंग प्रोग्राम जिससे आप का सरकार की कु-नीतियों में विश्वास बढ़ेगा | क्यों कि अकल का नाश, सब का विकास | लीजिए अब पेश है ख़ास प्रोग्राम -- मन की भड़ास |</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
</feed>
